[
  {
    "levelName": "Tutorial",
    "index": "0",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "",
            "answer": ""
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/TutorialFiles/TutorialPuzzleOneStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/TutorialFiles/TutorialPuzzleOneDirections",
        "puzzleName": "LevelOne",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "",
            "answer": "Printing from a function!"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/TutorialFiles/TutorialPuzzleTwoStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/TutorialFiles/TutorialPuzzleTwoDirections",
        "puzzleName": "LevelTwo",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "",
            "answer": "Hi"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/TutorialFiles/TutorialPuzzleThreeStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/TutorialFiles/TutorialPuzzleThreeDirections",
        "puzzleName": "LevelThree",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "levelName": "Variables",
    "index": "1",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "",
            "answer": "-5"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableOneStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableOneDirections",
        "puzzleName": "One",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "5"
          },
          {
            "problem": "10",
            "answer": "10"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableTwoStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableTwoDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Two",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "25"
          },
          {
            "problem": "10",
            "answer": "50"
          },
          {
            "problem": "-5",
            "answer": "-25"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableThreeStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableThreeDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Three",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "",
            "answer": "Hello World"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableFourStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableFourDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Four",
        "puzzleIndex": "3"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "",
            "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10]"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableFiveStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/VariablesFiles/VariablesVariableFiveDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Five",
        "puzzleIndex": "4"
      }
    ]
  },



  {
    "levelName": "Conditionals",
    "index": "2",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "6",
            "answer": "False"
          },
          {
            "problem": "-5",
            "answer": "True"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsOneStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsOneDirections",
        "puzzleName": "One",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "6",
            "answer": "Greater than 5"
          },
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "Less than or equal to 5"
          },
          {
            "problem": "-5",
            "answer": "Less than or equal to 5"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsTwoStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsTwoDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Two",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "120",
            "answer": "Greater than 100"
          },
          {
            "problem": "100",
            "answer": "Greater than 50"
          },
          {
            "problem": "51",
            "answer": "Greater than 50"
          },
          {
            "problem": "50",
            "answer": "Greater than 25"
          },
          {
            "problem": "25",
            "answer": "Less than 25"
          },
          {
            "problem": "20",
            "answer": "Less than 25"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsThreeStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsThreeDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Three",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "0",
            "answer": "Between 0 and 10"
          },
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "Between 0 and 10"
          },
          {
            "problem": "10",
            "answer": "Between 0 and 10"
          },
          {
            "problem": "11",
            "answer": "Between 11 and 20"
          },
          {
            "problem": "15",
            "answer": "Between 11 and 20"
          },
          {
            "problem": "20",
            "answer": "Between 11 and 20"
          },
          {
            "problem": "21",
            "answer": "Between 21 and 30"
          },
          {
            "problem": "25",
            "answer": "Between 21 and 30"
          },
          {
            "problem": "30",
            "answer": "Between 21 and 30"
          },
          {
            "problem": "-1",
            "answer": "Not between 0 and 30"
          },
          {
            "problem": "31",
            "answer": "Not between 0 and 30"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsFourStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsFourDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Four",
        "puzzleIndex": "3"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "100",
            "answer": "A"
          },
          {
            "problem": "90",
            "answer": "A"
          },
          {
            "problem": "89",
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "problem": "80",
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "problem": "79",
            "answer": "C"
          },
          {
            "problem": "70",
            "answer": "C"
          },
          {
            "problem": "69",
            "answer": "D"
          },
          {
            "problem": "60",
            "answer": "D"
          },
          {
            "problem": "59",
            "answer": "F"
          },
          {
            "problem": "20",
            "answer": "F"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsFiveStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ConditionalsFiles/ConditionalsConditionalsFiveDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Five",
        "puzzleIndex": "4"
      }
    ]
  },



  {
    "levelName": "Loops",
    "index": "3",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "0",
            "answer": "0"
          },
          {
            "problem": "1",
            "answer": "0"
          },
          {
            "problem": "2",
            "answer": "1"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "20",
            "answer": "190"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsOneStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsOneDirections",
        "puzzleName": "One",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "4"
          },
          {
            "problem": "6",
            "answer": "-1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "1",
            "answer": "0"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "57",
            "answer": "-1"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsTwoStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsTwoDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Two",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "0",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "1",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "3",
            "answer": "6"
          },
          {
            "problem": "4",
            "answer": "24"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "120"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsThreeStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsThreeDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Three",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "2, 10",
            "answer": "1024"
          },
          {
            "problem": "5, 5",
            "answer": "3125"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "1, 1",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "5, 6",
            "answer": "15625"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsFourStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsFourDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Four",
        "puzzleIndex": "3"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "1",
            "answer": "*\n"
          },
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "*****\n*****\n*****\n*****\n*****\n"
          },
          {
            "problem": "6",
            "answer": "******\n******\n******\n******\n******\n******\n"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "10",
            "answer": "**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n**********\n"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsFiveStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/LoopsFiles/LoopsFiveDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Five",
        "puzzleIndex": "4"
      }
    ]
  },



  {
    "levelName": "Strings",
    "index": "4",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"hello\"",
            "answer": "olleh"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"world\"",
            "answer": "dlrow"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"python\"",
            "answer": "nohtyp"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"ahhhhhhhh\"",
            "answer": "hhhhhhhha"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsOneStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsOneDirections",
        "puzzleName": "One",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"abcdefg\"",
            "answer": "aceg"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"123456\"",
            "answer": "135"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"python\"",
            "answer": "pto"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"12345678\"",
            "answer": "1357"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsTwoStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsTwoDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Two",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"hello\"",
            "answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"world\"",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"python\"",
            "answer": "1"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"zach\"",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"education\"",
            "answer": "5"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsThreeStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsThreeDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Three",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"radar\"",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"level\"",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"hello\"",
            "answer": "False"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"rotor\"",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"Zach\"",
            "answer": "False"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsFourStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsFourDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Four",
        "puzzleIndex": "3"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"hello world\", \"-\"",
            "answer": "hello-world"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"Python is great\", \"_\"",
            "answer": "Python_is_great"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"a b c\", \"*\"",
            "answer": "a*b*c"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"zach is cool\", \"_\"",
            "answer": "zach_is_cool"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsFiveStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/StringsFiles/StringsFiveDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Five",
        "puzzleIndex": "4"
      }
    ]
  },


  {
    "levelName": "Lists",
    "index": "5",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3]",
            "answer": "1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"]",
            "answer": "apple"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[4,5,6]",
            "answer": "4"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsOneStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsOneDirections",
        "puzzleName": "One",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3], 2",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"], \"grape\"",
            "answer": "False"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[5,6,7], 6",
            "answer": "True"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[5,6,7], 8",
            "answer": "False"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsTwoStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsTwoDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Two",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3]",
            "answer": "[3, 2, 1]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"]",
            "answer": "[\"cherry\", \"banana\", \"apple\"]"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[5, 6 ,7]",
            "answer": "[7, 6, 5]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[8, 9]",
            "answer": "[9, 8]"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsThreeStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsThreeDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Three",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2], [3, 4]",
            "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 4]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\"], [\"cherry\", \"date\"]",
            "answer": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\", \"date\"]"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[3, 4], [1, 2]",
            "answer": "[3, 4, 1, 2]"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsFourStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsFourDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Four",
        "puzzleIndex": "3"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3], 1",
            "answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[\"apple\", \"banana\", \"cherry\"], 2",
            "answer": "cherry"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3], 2",
            "answer": "3"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsFiveStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/ListsFiles/ListsFiveDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Five",
        "puzzleIndex": "4"
      }
    ]
  },





  {
    "levelName": "Functions",
    "index": "6",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "1, 5",
            "answer": "6"
          },
          {
            "problem": "1, 6",
            "answer": "7"
          },
          {
            "problem": "10, 10",
            "answer": "20"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "20, 20",
            "answer": "40"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/FunctionsFiles/FunctionsOneStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/FunctionsFiles/FunctionsOneDirections",
        "puzzleName": "One",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5]",
            "answer": "5"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 3, 40, 5]",
            "answer": "40"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 39, 40, 5]",
            "answer": "40"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[100, 1, 2, 3, 4]",
            "answer": "100"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/FunctionsFiles/FunctionsTwoStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/FunctionsFiles/FunctionsTwoDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Two",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      }
    ]
  },


  {
    "levelName": "Greek Myths",
    "index": "7",
    "puzzles": [
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1, 2, 20, 15, 3]",
            "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 15, 20]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[1, 5, 4, 3, 2]",
            "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[12, 5, 9, 3, 18, 1, 10, 15, 7, 2, 14, 20, 6, 8, 19, 11, 17, 4, 16, 13]",
            "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20]"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[2, 4, 40, 30, 6]",
            "answer": "[2, 4, 6, 30, 40]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[2, 10, 8, 6, 4]",
            "answer": "[2, 4, 6, 8, 10]"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[48, 20, 36, 12, 72, 4, 40, 60, 28, 8, 56, 80, 24, 32, 76, 44, 68, 16, 64, 52]",
            "answer": "[4, 8, 12, 16, 20, 24, 28, 32, 36, 40, 44, 48, 52, 56, 60, 64, 68, 72, 76, 80]"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/GreekMythsFiles/GreekMythsChaosStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/GreekMythsFiles/GreekMythsChaosDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Chaos",
        "puzzleIndex": "0"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"czggj\"",
            "answer": "hello"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"kizphjijpgomvhdxmjnxjkdxndgdxjqjgxvijxjidjndn\"",
            "answer": "pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "\"czggjczggj\"",
            "answer": "hellohello"
          },
          {
            "problem": "\"kizphjijpgomvhdxmjnxjkdxndgdxjqjgxvijxjidjndnkizphjijpgomvhdxmjnxjkdxndgdxjqjgxvijxjidjndn\"",
            "answer": "pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosispneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/GreekMythsFiles/GreekMythsFireStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/GreekMythsFiles/GreekMythsFireDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Fire",
        "puzzleIndex": "1"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1,3,2]",
            "answer": "-1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[1,5,4,3,2]",
            "answer": "-1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[1,3,4,5,6]",
            "answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[1,3,4,5,2,7]",
            "answer": "6"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[1,2,4,3,5,6,8,9,10]",
            "answer": "-1"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "[1,3,2,4]",
            "answer": "-1"
          },
          {
            "problem": "[1,3,4,5,2,6,8]",
            "answer": "3"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/GreekMythsFiles/GreekMythsHadesStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/GreekMythsFiles/GreekMythsHadesDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Hades",
        "puzzleIndex": "2"
      },
      {
        "testCases": [
          {
            "problem": "5",
            "answer": "5"
          },
          {
            "problem": "10",
            "answer": "55"
          },
          {
            "problem": "7",
            "answer": "13"
          },
          {
            "problem": "0",
            "answer": "0"
          }
        ],
        "hiddenTestCases": [
          {
            "problem": "6",
            "answer": "8"
          },
          {
            "problem": "9",
            "answer": "34"
          }
        ],
        "startingCode": "TextFiles/GreekMythsFiles/GreekMythsHadesStartingCode",
        "directions": "TextFiles/GreekMythsFiles/GreekMythsHadesDirections",
        "puzzleName": "Minotaur",
        "puzzleIndex": "3"
      }
    ]
  }
]
